timetap.com 2019-10-02

# Privacy Policy for Appointment Booking with TimeTap

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the timetap.com and Addy Systems LLC and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Addy Systems LLC include timetap.com and TimeTap. The TimeTap website is an Online booking software site. By using the TimeTap website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement..

### Sections of Privacy Policy

  * Collection of your Personal Information
  * Use of your Personal Information
  * General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
  * User Consent
  * Data Subject Rights
  * Use of Cookies
  * Security of your Personal Information
  * Children Under Thirteen
  * Disconnecting your TimeTap Account from Third Party Websites
  * Opt-Out & Unsubscribe
  * Changes to this Statement 
  * Contact Information

### Collection of your Personal Information

TimeTap may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase TimeTap's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. TimeTap may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender, political affiliation, race, religion and Defined by TimeTap's customers. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

TimeTap may automatically collect information about your computer hardware and software. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain the quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the TimeTap website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through TimeTap's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

TimeTap encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from TimeTap so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. TimeTap is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the TimeTap website.

### Use of your Personal Information

TimeTap collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

TimeTap may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from TimeTap and its affiliates. TimeTap may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

TimeTap does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

TimeTap may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to TimeTap, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

TimeTap may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within TimeTap, in order to determine what TimeTap services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within TimeTap to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. 

TimeTap will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on TimeTap or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of TimeTap; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of TimeTap, or the public.

### General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) is a new European Union (EU) privacy law that goes into effect on 25th May 2018. This new privacy law will replace the 1995 EU Data Protection Directive (DPD).

Its objective is to improve the protection of the personal data of EU citizens and ensure that organizations that collect, store and process Personally Identifiable Information (PII) – such as email addresses or phone numbers – operate in a well-defined framework. PII is any data that used alone or with other data can be used to identify a person.

[Click Here](https://gdpr-info.eu/) to find the complete breakdown of the GDPR new private laws.

Please reach out to our team if you have any question on how this affects the data held by TimeTap via [support@timetap.com](mailto:support@timetap.com) or 202-753-7351.

### User Consent

The purpose of the GDPR is to ensure that businesses, like TimeTap, have a legal basis to process Personal Data. TimeTap will do this by asking users for their consent and this consent must be specific and verifiable.

This means that a written record of consent must be kept and tied to specific users. It also means that this consent can be removed/taken away at any time and as a result businesses have to delete the PII from their records.

Consent also has to be unambiguous and clearly explain what the user is agreeing to. As an example, any form that has pre-checked consent boxes on it are not accepted by this new law. 

### Data Subject Rights

The new GDRP EU regulation clearly defines the rights of the data subjects, meaning the person whose data is held by a business. EU citizens will have the right to ask for information regarding how their data is processed, used and stored. In addition, they are able to request their data to be handled in a specific manner. As an example, they have the ability to control where their data is hosted.

Whatever the reasons they have the right to request their data to be corrected, amended or even deleted. They also have the right to access that data and the company they use hosts check with personal data.

This means that the data processors need to be clear on how they process data – including the different third party services they might be using – and be ready to support user requests in a timely manner.

### Use of Cookies

The TimeTap website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize TimeTap pages, or register with TimeTap site or services, a cookie helps TimeTap to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same TimeTap website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the TimeTap features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the TimeTap services or websites you visit.

### Security of your Personal Information

TimeTap secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

### Children Under Thirteen

TimeTap does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. 

### Disconnecting your TimeTap Account from Third Party Websites

You will be able to connect your TimeTap account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR TIMETAP ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users can disconnect from third party sites by clicking on the disconnect button. Users may also contact us via email or telephone.

### Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from TimeTap by contacting us here:

  * Web page: timetap.com/contact.html
  * Email: [support@timetap.com](mailto:support@timetap.com)
  * Phone: 202-753-7351

### Changes to this Statement

TimeTap will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. TimeTap encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how TimeTap is protecting your information.

### Contact Information

TimeTap welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that TimeTap has not adhered to this Statement, please contact TimeTap at:

Addy Systems LLC  
3705 Latrobe Dr.  
Suite 310,  
Charlotte, NC 28211

Email Address: [support@timetap.com](mailto:support@timetap.com)

Telephone number: 202-753-7351
